One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
Sabaody Archipelago
Grove #13
Kizaru Arrives
Ever since then, Monkey D. Luffy...
I've wanted to meet you someday.
Shanks...!
If Shanks hadn't told me all those things about you, I wouldn't have told you any of this either.
Anyway, you did well to make it this far.
He must be awaiting your arrival in the New World.
Really?
Yeah, he must be!
I wanna see him again, too!
Well, the situation is like this, so...
I was supposed to coat your ship, right?
Come to think of it, ship-coating costs a lot of money...
No, it's fine, Hachi.
I won't take any money from your friends.
That's good.
Thank you, Rayleigh.
I don't really get it, but it's great that he'll do it for free!
Thanks for that!
You're really generous!
Rayleigh-san...
Hmm?
I have a question.
Exactly what is the "Will of D"?
On the Poneglyph I saw on Sky Island...
Roger's name was engraved with the ancient language.
How did he know those letters?
I have come here, and I will lead these words to the end.
Pirate Gol D. Roger.
Do you people know what happened during the "void century" 900 years ago?
Yeah, we know.
We learned the entire history.
However, miss...
Don't be hasty.
Please push forward with your ship, one step at a time.
Perhaps we, as well as Ohara, were too impatient.
If I were to tell you the entire history here and now...
it's not like you could do anything the way you are now.
After you've taken your time to see the world...
The conclusion you'll reach might be different from what we found.
If you still want to hear it, then I'll tell you everything about the world now.
No, don't tell me.
I'll continue on the journey.
You'll see it all eventually.
It's too bad about what happened to your homeland, Ohara.
But Roger couldn't actually read those letters.
We were pirates.
We couldn't possibly compare to the genius Clover, or the other Oharans' intelligence.
He...
Could hear the "voice of all things".
That's all there is.
Hey, are you sure, Robin?
Didn't you just let a great chance slip away?!
Hey, old man!
I wanna ask something too!
The legendary treasure, One Piece...
Is it really...
Usopp!
I don't wanna hear where the treasure is!
I don't even wanna hear if there is a treasure or not!
I dunno anything about it, but everyone sets off to sea to find out for themselves!
If Pops were to tell us anything here, then I'll quit on becoming Pirate King!
If we're gonna have a boring adventure like that, then I won't do it!
Uh, I got it!
I got it!
Sorry, I just got carried away!
I don't wanna hear anything either!
Oh, yeah!
I've got the "I'll die if I hear anything about One Piece"-disease!
So don't you dare say anything, old man!
Can you do it?
The Grand Line far exceeds anything than you can imagine.
The enemies will be strong too.
Can you conquer such a terrifying sea?
I don't wanna conquer anything!
It's just that the person with the most freedom on the sea is the Pirate King!
I see.
I'm really a big fan of yours, Monkey-chan.
The ship is in Grove 41, right?
I'll be going there.
What about you?
The admiral is still coming to this island, you know.
We'll just cause trouble if we stay here...
So, let's go somewhere...
And shop!
Are you out of your mind?!
We're being chased, so we have to stay hidden!
She's right.
If we stay together, people will probably come after us.
In order to get off more smoothly, it'd be better for us to split up in town.
Then, we'll just randomly split up into groups and gather up there when he's done, right?
Talking about gathering up like it's a plan...
Whose mouth did that come from?
Shakki, you have that, right?
Yeah, I've got one.
This is a Vivrecard!
Oh, if you know about it, that makes things easier.
I'm a wanted man too...
So I think I'll move the ship from Grove 41 and work on it somewhere else.
The coating should take about three days.
It takes three whole days?
Your lives depend on my work, so that's the fastest I can do.
So, we have to survive for three days...
Scary!
Shall we say sunset in three days?
I'm not sure which grove I'll be in...
But just follow the Vivrecard, and I'll be waiting for you with the ship coated.
You'd better go buy whatever supplies you'll need for your underwater trip to Fishman Island.
Thanks a lot, Luffy-chin and everyone!
Really, thanks!
This all happened because of me, so sorry!
To show our gratitude, we'll show you the way to Fishman Island, so don't worry!
Watch out for the navy for the next three days!
Hachi, watch your health.
Let's meet again in three days.
I'll be there to send you off, okay?
See ya later, granny!
We're up against an admiral!
We'll have to make sure that none of us die, eh?
Don't say scary stuff like that!
Three days, huh?
Then, let's go...
To the amusement park!
Hey!
Take care!
Don't be too reckless!
Yeah, you too!
I'll leave Hachi to you!
I guess I should go, then.
Yeah, I'm counting on you!
But who'd have thought...
that we'd meet one of the Pirate King's crew mate in a place like this?
It surprised me.
How should I put it... He really left an impression, especially for a geezer.
Well, he is the most famous of Roger's crewmates, after all.
So he was a crew mate on the Oro Jackson, huh?
I did assist a man named Roger...
I'm glad I met him.
So, you're the type of guy who respects his elders?
It happens from time to time!
Hey...
Why don't we go to the amusement park?
Will you shut up?!
I want to go...
You, too?!
Sabaody Archipelago
Grove 27 Harbor
It's Admiral Kizaru!
We've got to run!
Capture the pirates!
Hello?
There are plenty of wanted pirates around!
Look out for those with bounties exceeding 100 million!
Run!
Hello? This is Kizaru...
Now, that's odd...
Navy Headquarters Admiral
"Kizaru" (Borsalino)
Hello?
How strange...
This is really bad!
If I...
If I were to take him down, I'd become famous at once!
Don't be a fool! He's one of the navy's strongest fighters!
Now! You...
Stop it!
Hello?
What?! Hey, I'm sure I just hit him!
It definitely passed through his head!
Now, that's really odd...
It's obvious that he's got some sort of ability!
There's no way a gun would work!
Run!
I'd like to ask you a question...
I'm looking for a man named Sentoumaru...
That guy's my subordinate, you see...
Sheesh, I was just asking...
Don't you think that's going too far, Kizaru-san?
You can't destroy the Yarukiman Mangroves!
Oops, seems like I overdid it...
He's totally messed up...
So, that's Admiral Kizaru?
Apoo-san! We're in trouble, too!
We have to get away!
You're such an idiot.
Where's the fun in just running away?
We've gotta upset the enemy before we go.
What are you planning to do?!
Requesting backup at the port!
What happened?
I don't know!
I have no idea, but all our troops...
have turned into children and old men!
What's going on?!
My back is killing me...
This is classic!
It's her doing!
The one with the bounty of 140 million: Jewelry Bonney!
Watch out for the rookies with bounties over 100 million!
You dog!
You're Capone "Gang" Bege, the guy with 138 million on your head, right?!
You'll never reach the sea!
What happened to your subordinates?! Are they moving independently?!
What an unlucky man you are... Surrender!
I've got you guys beaten...
when it comes to military might.
Oh, I'd like to ask you something...
K-Kizaru!
W-We'll take care of this...
Captain, please run away!
Do not panic.
I will not die today.
I'm telling you, we'll hide in the amusement park!
Stop lying.
You'd just play around, flashily at that.
Who're you?
We're under attack!
Don't just stand around!
Standby to attack!
Bring out the cannons!
Open the gates!
Commence attack!
What?!
Shoot!
What?
This guy's got something inside his body!
It got bigger...!
What's going on?!
He didn't even do anything!
Cavalry, charge!
Something's coming out of his stomach again!
An army is coming out!
Now it's horses?!
Capone "Gang" Bege...
What kind of power does he have?!
Firing squad, take aim!
What's with the smoke?
Father, there's too much smoke!
Like I said, I've got you outnumbered!
Sabaody Archipelago
Grove 27 Harbor
Hurry up and run!
It seems that the Seven Warlords are on the move!
Seriously? Who?
The Seven Warlords?!
Grove 24
I suppose they won't let us pass Navy HQ...
But!
I've got a bit of a stubborn streak!
Island Grove 24
I'm begging you. Run, Captain Hawkins!
Captain Hawkins!
Battle: Probability of defeat, 100%...
Do you have a moment?
Escape: Probability of success, 12%...
I'm trying to find a man named Sentoumaru...
Defense: Probability of evasion, 76%...
I do not know that man.
Please ask someone else.
Well, if I can't find him...
I won't have anything to do...
And with that being the case, there's no way I'd let someone with a bounty like yours, go free.
A bounty of 249 million, "The Mage", Basil Hawkins...
Speed is weight.
Have you ever experienced a light-speed kick?
Captain!
Grove 27
What happened?!
Hey, what happened?!
I don't know! He just suddenly flew off!
Grove 24
He's really strong.
Hey, is he still gonna fight?!
Archipelago Harbor
Hey, what was that?
He just suddenly...
He must have been attacked from somewhere...
Grove 24
Captain!
I should have guessed, you are far stronger than I imagined.
How odd...
You've beaten two already...
Having only ten bodies against an admiral is pretty discouraging...
That's the "Mad Monk", Urouge!
Not just him!
That's one of the Seven Warlords, Bartholomew Kuma!
He got me... He's too strong!
Don't tell me... that's Kizaru?!
I've got terrible luck!
A navy admiral in front of me...
A Warlord behind me...
Is this the end for me?!
I wouldn't say that.
I still do not see the mark of death upon you.
Really?
Hawkins from North Blue, huh?
You may be my enemy, but I appreciate the joke!
What? Another one showed up!
That's "Red Flag", X-Drake!
Why?!
Rear admiral, Drake...
Damn, I didn't intend to meet Kizaru!
I'm pretty badly beaten, but let's see...
if there really is some hope of victory!
Now, it's time for my counterattack!
Look! This has become quite the situation.
Now, this is interesting!
We're in trouble!
Those guys are all gonna die!
This is our chance to run, right?!
What're you saying?
This is where the fun begins!
Grove 12
Who're you?
Stand back, Luffy!
He's one of the Seven Warlords!
Seven Warlords?
How do you know?
No matter what, don't let that attack hit you!
It's a shockwave!
What's this?!
He could even do this?!
Hey, that's not a shockwave!
That's a...
Beam!
This is no time to be happy!
Bartholomew Kuma... Why is he here again?!
That bastard...!
Is he that guy who showed up afterwards on Thriller Bark?!
Yeah, that's him!
Back then, he made some shockwave from the pads on his hand and caused us a lot of trouble!
He was planning to eliminate us there, but...
I guess he realized we survived and came back!
Back then, you sure got us good!
Coup de Vent
It worked!
No.
Luffy-san!
Gear Second
I already know you're strong, so I'll go all-out right away!
We've got no choice!
Something's strange...
He feels different from back then...
Is it just my imagination?
Let's go!
Grove 36
He's late!
The warships should be here by now...
That's strange...
Why hasn't he contacted me yet, that old man Kizaru...
If he doesn't hurry up...
I'll have to...
finish off all those rookies!
Translation, Yibis
Soundtracking, Halee
Editing, Feeso
Infoboxes, BernieCrane
Formatting, Sewil, Datenshi
Edit-checking, Galaxy 9000